With the help of Caesar's Bandana,
JoJo barely managed to defeat Wamu.
Then, it was Kars' turn to face Lisa
Lisa in their one-on-one combat.
Suddenly, Von Stroheim showed
up to battle the vampires,
along with Speedwagon and Smokey.
In a cowardly turn, Kars used
a double to deceive Lisa Lisa.
Then he literally stabbed her in the
back to use as a pawn against Jojo.
Jojo and Lisa Lisa are in the
greatest peril of their lives.
Kars, you bastard!
There's a place waiting for you in hell!
Jojo doesn't know.
He doesn't know the woman
he's trying to save.
It's his mother!
You don't want to let go of that, Jojo.
It's a forest of crystal
spikes down there.
She would die horribly.
Kaz!
You have lived for far too long!
Your soul's decayed.
It's like a pumpkin left
to rot out in a dead field.
Even flies avoid it.
Yes, grumble at me.
Shout your lungs out.
Heave your insults at me.
For as long as you're holding
on to that rope, my friend,
that's about all you can do.
Shijima no Seiko kara
Diego o koe
Shinku no chishin o ga
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Jojo! Lisa! Lisa!
He can't follow what's really going on.
He doesn't realize that's
his mother he's holding.
Mr.
Speedwagon, we need to tell Jojo!
Not yet. But why not?
It's not the proper time.
Von Stroheim!
Have you finished disposing
of those vampires yet?
We must help Jojo!
Yeah, right!
You think I just have to wave my magic
flashlight and then it's all done?
Out of sight and out of mind!
Von Stroheim has got his
hands full right now.
Jojo.
Careful now.
That rope looks like it's
starting to slip a little.
As long as you're holding
on so tightly to that rope,
Your clumsy feet have limited reach.
Oh, no!
His kick did make it to Kars,
but there was no Hormone.
We're in real trouble.
You poor boy.
It looks like you're
running out of Hormone.
But it is possible you might have enough
left to make one last-ditch attack on me.
I'll walk up there,
and then I'm going to take
your life as easily as if
I were plucking a little
flower along a garden pathway.
Cause! Hmm?
Maybe there is enough left in me.
Enough, Hamon, for one
last desperate attack.
To be honest, even I don't know. Hmm?
But either way, I've
devised a cunning plan.
I guarantee it's something
to make you choke.
How badly do you want to know what it is?
Cause I'm not telling! Hey!
I can see that you've stopped
tying those ropes together now.
You see this match?
What do you think I'm going
to be doing with this fire?
Huh?
What on earth is JoJo thinking?
He set his scarf on fire!
Before this flame has a chance to burn me,
I'm going to find a way to use whatever
I can to send you straight to hell.
The scarf is a gamble.
Something to motivate me.
A little pain to help me find a way.
Jojo, come on now.
You can't fool me.
That's just an act of desperation!
Don't toy with me, you're just dodging
around for a chance to catch your breath.
It's no matter, I'm taking your
life at the moment of my choice.
I'm tired of dealing
with your silly antics.
Oh come on, I need to breathe.
So what if I look silly doing it?
Jojo, look.
Clearly I can sever Lisa Lisa's rope.
With just a flick of my wrist!
And if you dodge me again?
That is exactly what I will do.
What do you think?
Should I press just a little harder?
Hmm?
It's so easy!
Is that what you want?
Don't do it!
You ran away before?
Now come toward me slowly.
Or you could stay where you are and
watch as I cut through the line.
The coward!
So, what then?
Is your life more precious than that
of the woman dangling down there?
Here's my choice!
I don't know what you think you're
doing, but when I cut this line?
You will both be impaled on the
crystal spikes below, you fool!
Jojo Lisa Lisa!
Idiot!
Two birds with one cut!
What?
But he!
This rope!
It's connected to Jojo!
When did he make this happen?
He didn't have enough time to! Oh!
When he first kicked at me, he allowed
himself to be cut along with the rope.
And then when he ignited
that damned match,
he secretly tied his leg
to the rope on Lisa Lisa.
I see it now.
He needed some kind of distraction.
That's when he set his scarf on fire.
And then to tie the lines together,
he maneuvered me into doing his work
for him by cutting Lisa Lisa's rope.
That manipulating cheat!
Now you're the one saving
both me and Lisa Lisa!
You deceived me, Jojo!
How odd that I should hear you
complaining about trickery!
You enjoy deceiving others, but
now the shoe's on the other foot!
You may have lived for over 10,000 years,
but if you're going up against my
skills, you need another decade!
You're thrown!
Harmon!
Over!
Drive!
Did it work?
That was the last of my Harmon.
I'm burned out.
I don't have an ounce of strength left.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Yes!
It was enough! Oh, yes! He did it!
He hit cars with his hormone!
Off you go!
I'll get you!
Oh, look at that!
Chaos fell right onto
his own crystal spikes!
Wah-ha-ha-ha!
The pillar man is done! See?
The Hamon will travel right
up his arm and do the job!
You're weak, your time on Earth is up!
A mere human could finish you off now!
Yeah!
Trying to spook us, eh?
Now, let's eliminate him forever!
Bring out the Ultraviolet Amplifier!
Lisa Lisa...
Kar said that he wasn't actually
planning to kill you with his blade,
so I don't think that
your wounds are fatal.
We need to get you taken care of quickly,
but I don't think this is
the day you're going to die.
It's finally done.
Looks like it, and I'm glad.
Say, Mr.
Speedwagon, um, can I please
ask you something? Of course.
Well, why did Granny Arena lie to Jojo?
Why'd she tell him that his mother
had died when he was a little boy?
Why does Lisa Lisa hide her past
and not tell him who she really is?
Smokey, that's, uh...
I know Granny Arena told me not to ask
you, but I've got to figure this out.
I mean, she is his mother.
Keeping that information
from him is just awful.
Smokey.
JoJo and Granny Arena, they're my friends.
Back in New York, they both saved me.
I was just a lowly pickpocket,
but they helped me out anyway.
That's the reason I'm here.
I'm going to do anything I can to help.
All right then, Smokey.
Let me tell you, in New York you
proved what a good friend you were.
You took excellent care
of Iran while I was gone.
But this you can never reveal to Jojo.
This is the business
of the Joestar family.
Friends or not, we don't have
the right to talk about it.
The name Lisa Lisa is made up.
An alias.
Her real given name is Elizabeth.
Raised and trained by the
Harmon user Straitzo you met.
She and Irina's son, George
Joestar, fell in love.
They got married.
Soon, George and Elizabeth had a son.
You know him as Jojo.
Jojo's father, George, enlisted as a
member of Britain's Royal Flying Corps.
Aviation developed rapidly during
the First World War and George
was among the brave pilots to
fly into battle in the skies.
He stood out as a hero even among the
members of the Royal Flying Corps.
It was then that a gut-wrenching
horror from the past
came back to haunt the
members of the Joestar family.
Fifty years earlier, Dio Brando
created blood-sucking zombies.
Straitzo, myself, and the others
believed that we had exterminated them.
But one of them had escaped.
He hid himself within society and
lived for decades undiscovered.
He was cunning, intelligent,
supremely dangerous.
He created no spawn.
He devoured the bones
and hair of his victims,
leaving behind no
evidence of his existence.
And by some wretched,
wicked twist of fate,
he had placed himself in position as
a commander in the Royal Flying Corps.
The Royal Flying Corps?
With Jojo's father?
The very same.
George was observant and figured this out.
He had listened well
to Straitzo and myself,
but ultimately, George
was only an ordinary man.
He had character and talent, but he
had no training in the ways of Hormone.
Before he was able to
unmask the commander.
He was discovered by his monstrous quarry.
His message to Straitzo was too late.
George's death was covered up.
As an unfortunate night time plane crash.
Straitzo and I found this suspicious.
So we investigated.
and eventually learn the truth.
That night, Elizabeth held an infant Jojo
as I told her what we had discovered.
Instead of showing grief,
she ran out intent on bloody revenge.
She was a genius with Harmon, but
she let her emotions consume her.
She was careless.
There was a witness to
the commander's death.
The military knew nothing
about zombies or Harmon.
They concluded that for
some unknown reason,
Elizabeth had attacked their
beloved commander, killed him,
then burned his body to hide the crime.
Words spread as only bad news can.
and soon she was known around
the world as a murderer?
and traitor to the war effort.
We used all the resources of the
Speedwagon Foundation to cover her trail.
Elizabeth had to leave England behind,
without even a word of goodbye to her son.
Erina knew what had occurred, and
she gave me this specific request.
When the child grows up
and asks about his parents,
please tell him they both died in the war.
This child...
Poor little child.
And so it was that
Elizabeth became Lisa Lisa.
Why why is it that way
at least let him know
his mother's not dead
somewhere I know painfully?
I will, why?
Iran lost her husband and her son in the
battle between Harmon and the Stone Masks.
But thinking of her grandson,
her Joseph, her Jojo...
She didn't want Harmon to create
yet another hole in her life.
Lisa Lisa feels the same.
What tragedy for this family.
Such a miserable fortune.
But now, it's better.
Jojo used Hamon positively
to save his mother's life!
Mr.
Speedwagon,
there's no reason for Lisa Lisa to
hide the truth from Jojo any longer.
He already knows about Hamon.
And he used it to save his mother's life.
That's true.
But still, it's not my decision to make.
It's a question of how
Iran and Lisa Lisa feel.
I guess. Major!
We're ready to fire, sir!
Excellent.
Everyone focus on him.
Und now we will share the honor
of executing cars. Jawohl!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Now, Ghaz, die!
I can't begin to tell you how good
it feels to give this order myself!
Von Stroheim, you must stop!
He's got the redstone attached
right there on his mask!
UV light will help him!
No, dammit!
Stop now!
Don't fire the UV out of the fire!
He's got me!
I didn't see him with the mask.
I didn't know that he
had it anywhere near him.
I didn't see him put in the red stone.
No, it can't be.
Dear God.
Kars.
I'll feed you round about.
The words will make you out and out!
You'll spend the day your way.
Calling money, money, fuel,
summer, middle of the valley?
Living around the lake.
Moms come out of the
sky, they stand there.
Why am I alone?
We'll be there, we'll see you
Tell them to some of we'll be
there, you'll be there too?
24, 24, while you will sing!
I'll be there with you.
He has become the Ubermensch.
He has complete mastery over organic life.
Is there really no way to stop him, Mr.
Speedwagon?
Cars the pillar man is no more!
He's become Cars, the ultimate creation.